forextips.com 2003-08-12

# forex training and education, about mti market traders institute currency money traders lessons tutorials and online trading

**  
**

  * **Refund of Tuition Fees** MTI will make a full refund of tuition fees in the following circumstances:   

  *  Application for a student visa is unsuccessful; or

  *  Program ceases to be provided at any time after it starts but before it is completed; or 

  *  Program does not commence on the agreed starting day; or

  *  Program is not provided in full because of the cancellation, or

  *  An offer of a place is withdrawn by MTI; or

  *  Applicant is unable to satisfy prescribed conditions stipulated in the Offer Conditions. 

**Refund of course materials**

  * Prior to shipping, you may cancel or modify an order at any time, without   
penalty. Please note that although we generally ship within 24hrs of   
receipt of your payment. Please notify us as soon as possible via email   
or phone Include your order number

  * We will replace any item that was damaged during shipping,

  * Refunds for purchases paid by credit card will be credited back to the   
card account. 

           **Refund of Subscription**

  * Payment Type:   
Payments for ForexTips.com services are accepted by credit card only. Your payment will be charged to your credit card account each month on the 25th of the month prior to the month of the service you are paying for.

  * Subscribers may begin the program at any time and the cost will be pro-rated. If you begin your subscription on the 1st of the month, the cost is as described above. Payment will be due and payable as previously outlined.

  * Subscriptions to ForexTips.com will be billed to your credit card on file automatically until you have canceled you subscription. Payment for subsequent monthly periods must be received prior to the expiration of the current monthly period. In the event that payment is not received before the expiration date, access will be restricted until payment has been received. 

NOTICE: If you wish to cancel, you must cancel in writing by email, mail or fax on or before the 24th of the month prior to the end of any current monthly subscription period.

There are no refunds of any previous payments.

Use of ForexTips.com requires the submission of personal data. However, in order to take advantage of certain personalized features, you will be required to submit a simple registration, including some information about yourself. Please read on for details about our privacy policy, what information we may collect and how we use it.  

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [**ForexTips.Com** ](http://www.forextips.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Uses of Registration Information**

Basic registration requires you to provide us a screen name and password, as well as some demographic information and a current email address. This information will then gain you access to the ForexTips.com real-time members services area. You will also have access to any new tools we may offer in the future. The information you provide us helps us administer these features. You are free to use as your screen name your real name or a set of characters you find easy to remember. For contests or promotions occasionally offered on the site, ForexTips.com may ask participants for additional personal data necessary to run the contest or notify winners. Any information you may provide to third parties in the course of purchasing any products and services which may be featured on ForexTips.com, is subject to the privacy policies of those organizations.

** Privacy of Personal Data on ForexTips.com**

No data you provide ForexTips.com as part of your basic registration or personalization will be sold to outside organizations. ForexTips.com, however, reserves the right to disclose personal identifying information when required or permitted by law. The information is stored on secure servers. You may occasionally receive from us at your designated email address notifications of new ForexTips.com features or offers. You may opt out of receiving those notifications by notifying us of personal preferences. Please remember to change your personal preferences for each email address that you may have registered with us.

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

** Cookie Policy**

We use cookie technology to help members move faster through the site and to keep track of your shopping cart. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. A cookie is a small file sent to your computer by the ForexTips.com site server. The most commonly employed cookies on ForexTips.com are those that help us establish (1) whether you are a registered member of ForexTips.com, and (2) whether a registered member has opted to use the "auto-login" feature, which eliminates the need for registered members to identify themselves each time they visit. A separate cookie from the company that handles our advertising production and tracking system helps identify which ad you may be clicking on, so that you will be linked to the right site. We may also use cookie technology to track the site's aggregate page views, which helps us determine which features the user base seems to be most or least interested in. An important point: We do not track your individual usage patterns using cookies, nor do we use them to track your financial holdings or other personal preferences in any individually identified way. Contrary to what you might have heard from other sources, cookies cannot get information from your hard drive against your will, cannot destroy files and cannot send you viruses.

#### Order Forms

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Children's Guidelines

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent

  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:

    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.

    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.

    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.

  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.

  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.

  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.

  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.

  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.

  1. You can send email to [tipshelp@forextips.com](mailto:tipshelp@forextips.com) Contacting the Web Site. 

  2.  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [tipshelp@forextips.com](mailto:tipshelp@forextips.com)

**  
**

  * **Refund of Tuition Fees** MTI will make a full refund of tuition fees in the following circumstances:   

  *  Application for a student visa is unsuccessful; or

  *  Program ceases to be provided at any time after it starts but before it is completed; or 

  *  Program does not commence on the agreed starting day; or

  *  Program is not provided in full because of the cancellation, or

  *  An offer of a place is withdrawn by MTI; or

  *  Applicant is unable to satisfy prescribed conditions stipulated in the Offer Conditions. 

**Refund of course materials**

  * Prior to shipping, you may cancel or modify an order at any time, without   
penalty. Please note that although we generally ship within 24hrs of   
receipt of your payment. Please notify us as soon as possible via email   
or phone Include your order number

  * We will replace any item that was damaged during shipping,

  * Refunds for purchases paid by credit card will be credited back to the   
card account. 

           **Refund of Subscription**

  * Payment Type:   
Payments for ForexTips.com services are accepted by credit card only. Your payment will be charged to your credit card account each month on the 25th of the month prior to the month of the service you are paying for.

  * Subscribers may begin the program at any time and the cost will be pro-rated. If you begin your subscription on the 1st of the month, the cost is as described above. Payment will be due and payable as previously outlined.

  * Subscriptions to ForexTips.com will be billed to your credit card on file automatically until you have canceled you subscription. Payment for subsequent monthly periods must be received prior to the expiration of the current monthly period. In the event that payment is not received before the expiration date, access will be restricted until payment has been received. 

NOTICE: If you wish to cancel, you must cancel in writing by email, mail or fax on or before the 24th of the month prior to the end of any current monthly subscription period.

There are no refunds of any previous payments.

Use of ForexTips.com requires the submission of personal data. However, in order to take advantage of certain personalized features, you will be required to submit a simple registration, including some information about yourself. Please read on for details about our privacy policy, what information we may collect and how we use it.  

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [**ForexTips.Com** ](http://www.forextips.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Uses of Registration Information**

Basic registration requires you to provide us a screen name and password, as well as some demographic information and a current email address. This information will then gain you access to the ForexTips.com real-time members services area. You will also have access to any new tools we may offer in the future. The information you provide us helps us administer these features. You are free to use as your screen name your real name or a set of characters you find easy to remember. For contests or promotions occasionally offered on the site, ForexTips.com may ask participants for additional personal data necessary to run the contest or notify winners. Any information you may provide to third parties in the course of purchasing any products and services which may be featured on ForexTips.com, is subject to the privacy policies of those organizations.

** Privacy of Personal Data on ForexTips.com**

No data you provide ForexTips.com as part of your basic registration or personalization will be sold to outside organizations. ForexTips.com, however, reserves the right to disclose personal identifying information when required or permitted by law. The information is stored on secure servers. You may occasionally receive from us at your designated email address notifications of new ForexTips.com features or offers. You may opt out of receiving those notifications by notifying us of personal preferences. Please remember to change your personal preferences for each email address that you may have registered with us.

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

** Cookie Policy**

We use cookie technology to help members move faster through the site and to keep track of your shopping cart. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. A cookie is a small file sent to your computer by the ForexTips.com site server. The most commonly employed cookies on ForexTips.com are those that help us establish (1) whether you are a registered member of ForexTips.com, and (2) whether a registered member has opted to use the "auto-login" feature, which eliminates the need for registered members to identify themselves each time they visit. A separate cookie from the company that handles our advertising production and tracking system helps identify which ad you may be clicking on, so that you will be linked to the right site. We may also use cookie technology to track the site's aggregate page views, which helps us determine which features the user base seems to be most or least interested in. An important point: We do not track your individual usage patterns using cookies, nor do we use them to track your financial holdings or other personal preferences in any individually identified way. Contrary to what you might have heard from other sources, cookies cannot get information from your hard drive against your will, cannot destroy files and cannot send you viruses.

#### Order Forms

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Children's Guidelines

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent

  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:

    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.

    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.

    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.

  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.

  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.

  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.

  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.

  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.

  1. You can send email to [tipshelp@forextips.com](mailto:tipshelp@forextips.com) Contacting the Web Site. 

  2.  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [tipshelp@forextips.com](mailto:tipshelp@forextips.com)
